condo.com 2013-05-23

# Condos For Sale - Apartments for Rent - Vacation Rentals - C: Condo.com™

We know you're concerned about protecting your privacy online. So are we. At Condo.com, we treat your personal information with the highest degree of safety and security.  

This policy explains how we collect information about you and how we use that information. We also outline the choices you have. By conducting business on Condo.com, you accept the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, contact us via e-mail at [support@condo.com](mailto:support@condo.com).

 _How Secure is My Information?_ **  
**  
 **Protecting your personal information:**  
Condo.com pledges a safe and secure transaction experience for all Users on our site. We use the industry standard for Internet security, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL 128-bit) encryption to scramble your personal and credit card information as it travels over the Internet during the sales transaction process. This encryption makes it difficult for anyone to read your information in transit. We protect all of your personal information, including your name, address, password and credit card information. 

**  
Protecting your credit card information:**   
Secure Sockets Layer (SSL 128-bit) encryption scrambles your credit card number when you submit your order. This encryption makes your information unreadable as it travels over the Internet. 

**  
Protecting your password:**  
If you forget your password, you can create a new one. You can do your part to protect your personal information by keeping your password a secret and making sure you log off completely if you share a computer.

 _Personal Information_

 **What we gather:**  
We need your name, billing address, mailing address, e-mail address, billing phone number, mailing phone number and credit card number to process your transactions on the site. An e-mail confirmation will be sent once registered and billing information has been accepted. If we have a question about your listing or purchase activities, we may contact you by e-mail or by phone. 

In addition, we may use your information to recommend condos and other products or services based on your criteria, to personalize our newsletters if you choose to subscribe, to maintain your account and to improve your site experience. 

**  
Who we share it with:**   
Condo.com may sell, rent or give information about you to third parties for them to use for themselves or their affiliates without your prior permission. We may use or provide your contact information to third-party advertisers that may contact you by email, mobile messaging or SMS. We may also disclose aggregate customer information (such as number of visits or average order amounts) to advertisers or other third parties. We may also share customer contact information with our affiliate marketing partners upon a user's request for additional information on the site.  

 **  
Special Services and Promotions:**   
If you want to participate in Condo.com special promotions, you must enter your name and e-mail address. We will add your e-mail address to our customer newsletter mailing list and give you the option to sign up for additional Email Sponsored Newsletters such as our CondoFinder™ service. You always have the option to unsubscribe.

 **  
Contacting** Condo.com **Customer Service:**   
If you contact Condo.com Customer Service, we will use your name, e-mail address, phone number and transaction history to answer your questions or solve your problem. On occasion, we may contact you later to verify information or to check on the quality of your Customer Service contact.

 **  
Legal Requests:**   
We may release customer account or other information if we're advised that such release is necessary to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Condo.com or law enforcement for loss prevention and credit risk reduction. 

**  
**_What about My Account?_

 **Creating an Account:**  
Creating an account makes it fast and easy to list, buy, sell or lease condos on Condo.com. A Condo.com account provides you with the ability to: establish listings, access to view favorite properties and create a personal inbox and outbox for communicating with other Buyers, Sellers, Brokers and Developers within Condo.com. You also have the option to sign up for email notification services.   

**  
Option to change, modify or delete account information:**  
You can review, modify or delete your account information anytime. We give you the option to look over your account profile information, if you've created an account, as well the ability to modify or change information or delete your account entirely. 

Contact Condo.com if you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with Condo.com. E-mail us at [support@condo.com](mailto:support@condo.com), or call us toll-free at: 877.CONDO.01 (877.266.3601).

 ** **Third Party Advertisers, Your Opt-out Rights:**** **** **** **  
We use  **third-party companies to serve advertisements and collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit Condo.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to Condo.com and other websites in order to provide advertisements on Condo.com, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about the practices of some of these third party advertising companies and learn which of these companies allow you to opt-out of this type of information collection, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp#).
